A Guide to the Military Rule Election Records of the Virginia Secretary of the Commonwealth, 1867, 1869
Library of Virginia
- Highland County
  - Poll lists (1st and 2nd Districts), 1869. (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Poll lists (3rd and 4th Districts), 1869. (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Poll lists (5th District), 1869. (Box 18, Folder 4)
- Isle of Wight County
  - Ballots, 1867. (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Election certificates, 1867. (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Poll books (All Districts), 1867. (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Ballots, 1869. (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Poll lists (1st - 3rd Districts), 1869. (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Poll lists (4th and 5th Districts), 1869. (Box 18, Folder 10)
- James City County
  - Election certificates, 1867. (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Poll books (All Districts), 1867. (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Ballots, 1869. (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Poll lists (All Districts), 1869. (Box 18, Folder 14)
- King and Queen County
  - Ballots, 1869. (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Poll lists (1st District), 1869. (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Poll lists (2nd and 3rd Districts), 1869. (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - Poll lists (4th District), 1869. (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - Poll lists (5th District), 1869. (Box 18, Folder 19)
- King George County
  - Ballots, 1867. (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Election certificates, 1867. (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Poll books (All Districts), 1867. (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Ballots, 1869. (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Poll lists (All Districts), 1869. (Box 19, Folder 5)
- King William County
  - Poll books (1st and 2nd Districts), 1867. (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Poll books (3rd and 4th Districts), 1867. (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Ballots, 1869. (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Poll lists (1st and 2nd Districts), 1869. (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Poll lists (3rd and 4th Districts), 1869. (Box 19, Folder 10)
- Lancaster County
  - Election certificates, 1867. (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Poll books (1st District), 1867. (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Poll books (2nd District), 1867. (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Poll books (3rd District), 1867. (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Poll books (4th District), 1867. (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Ballots, 1869. (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - Oaths/Affidavits of residence, 1869. (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - Poll lists (1st District), 1869. (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - Poll lists (2nd District), 1869. (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - Poll lists (3rd District), 1869. (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - Poll lists (4th District), 1869. (Box 19, Folder 21)
- Lee County
  - Election certificates, 1867. (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Poll books (1st - 4th District), 1867. (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Poll books (5th - 7th Districts), 1867. (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Ballots, 1869. (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Poll lists (1st District), 1869. (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Poll lists (2nd District), 1869. (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Poll lists (3rd District), 1869. (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Poll lists (4th District), 1869. (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Poll lists (5th District), 1869. (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Poll lists (6th District), 1869. (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Poll lists (7th District), 1869. (Box 20, Folder 11)
- Loudoun County
  - Ballots, 1869. (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Poll lists (1st and 2nd Districts), 1869. (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Poll lists (3rd District), 1869. (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Poll lists (4th District), 1869. (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Poll lists (5th District), 1869. (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - Poll lists (6th District), 1869. (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - Poll lists (7th District), 1869. (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - Poll lists (8th and 9th Districts), 1869. (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - Poll lists (10th District), 1869. (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - Poll lists (Unidentified District) 1869. (Box 20, Folder 21)
- Louisa County
  - Ballots, 1867. (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Election certificates, 1867. (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Poll books (1st - 4th Districts), 1867. (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Poll books (5th - 8th Districts), 1867. (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Ballots, 1869. (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Poll lists (1st and 2nd District), 1869. (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Poll lists (3rd District), 1869. (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Poll lists (4th District), 1869. (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Poll lists (5th and 6th Districts), 1869. (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Poll lists (7th and 8th Districts), 1869. (Box 21, Folder 10)
- Madison County
  - Election certificates, 1867. (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Poll books (1st and 2nd Districts), 1867. (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Poll books (3rd and 4th Districts), 1867. (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Ballots, 1869. (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Poll lists (1st District), 1869. (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Poll lists (2nd District), 1869. (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Poll lists (3rd and 4th Districts), 1869. (Box 21, Folder 17)
- Mathews County
  - Ballots, 1867. (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Election certificates, 1867. (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Poll books (1st District), 1867. (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Poll books (2nd District), 1867. (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Poll books (3rd District), 1867. (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Ballots, 1869. (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Poll lists (1st District), 1869. (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Poll lists (2nd District), 1869. (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Poll lists (3rd District), 1869. (Box 22, Folder 9)
- Mecklenburg County
  - Election certificates, 1867. (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Poll books (1st and 2nd Districts), 1867. (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Poll books (3rd and 4th Districts), 1867. (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Poll books (5th and 6th Districts), 1867. (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - Poll books (7th and 8th Districts), 1867. (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - Poll lists (1st and 2nd Districts), 1869. (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Poll lists (3rd District), 1869. (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Poll lists (4th District), 1869. (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Poll lists (5th and 6th Districts), 1869. (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Poll lists (7th District), 1869. (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Poll lists (8th District), 1869. (Box 23, Folder 6)
- Middlesex County
  - Election certificates, 1867. (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Poll books (All Districts), 1867. (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Ballots, 1869. (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Poll lists (All Districts), 1869. (Box 23, Folder 10)
- Montgomery County
  - Election certificates, 1867. (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Poll books (All Districts), 1867. (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Ballots, 1869. (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - Poll lists (1st District), 1869. (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - Poll lsits (2nd District), 1869. (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - Poll lists (3rd District), 1869. (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - Poll lists (4th District), 1869. (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Poll lists (5th District), 1869. (Box 24, Folder 2)
- Nansemond County
  - Election certificates, 1867. (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Poll books (1st and 2nd Districts), 1867. (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Poll books (3rd and 4th Districts), 1867. (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Poll books (5th District), 1867. (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Ballots, 1869. (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Poll lists (1st District), 1869. (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Poll lists (2nd District), 1869. (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Poll lists (3rd District), 1869. (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Poll lists (4th District), 1869. (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Poll lsits (5th District), 1869. (Box 24, Folder 12)
- Nelson County
  - Election certificates, 1867. (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Poll books (1st and 2nd Districts), 1867. (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Poll books (3rd and 4th Districts), 1867. (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Poll books (5th and 6th Districts), 1867. (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Ballots, 1869. (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Poll lists (1st - 3rd Districts), 1869. (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Poll lists (4th District), 1869. (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Poll lists (5th District), 1869. (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Poll lists (6th District), 1869. (Box 25, Folder 9)
- Norfolk County
  - Election certificates, 1867. (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Poll books (1st and 2nd Districts), 1867. (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Poll books (3rd and 4th Districts), 1867. (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - Poll books (5th and 6th Districts), 1867. (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - Ballots, 1869. (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - Poll lists (1st District), 1869. (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - Poll lists (2nd - 4th Districts), 1869. (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - Poll lists (5th and 6th Districts), 1869. (Box 25, Folder 17)
- Northampton County
  - Poll books and election certificates (All Districts), 1867. (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Ballots, 1869. (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Poll lists (1st District), 1869. (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Poll lists (2nd District), 1869. (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Poll lists (3rd District), 1869. (Box 26, Folder 5)
- Nottoway County
  - Election certificates, 1867. (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Poll books (1st District), 1867. (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Poll books (2nd District), 1867. (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Poll books (3rd District), 1867. (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Poll books (4th District), 1867. (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Ballots, 1869. (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Poll lists (1st District), 1867. (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - Poll lists (2nd - 4th Districts), 1869. (Box 26, Folder 13)
- Orange County
  - Poll lists (1st and 2nd Districts), 1869. (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - Poll lists (3rd District), 1869. (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - Poll lists (4th District), 1869. (Box 26, Folder 16)
  - Poll lists (5th District), 1869. (Box 26, Folder 17)
- Page County
  - Election certificates, 1867. (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Poll books (1st and 2nd Districts), 1867. (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Poll books (3rd and 4th Districts), 1867. (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Ballots, 1869. (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Poll lists (1st District), 1869. (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Poll lists (2nd District), 1869. (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Poll lists (3rd District), 1869. (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Poll lists (4th District), 1869. (Box 27, Folder 8)
- Pittsylvania County
  - Ballots, 1867. (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Poll books and election certificates (1st and 2nd Districts), 1867. (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Poll books and election certificates (3rd District), 1867. (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Poll books and election certificates (4th District), 1867. (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - Poll books and election certificates (5th and 6th Districts), 1867. (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - Poll books and election certificates (7th and 8th Districts), 1867. (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - Poll books and election certificates (9th and 10th Districts), 1867. (Box 27, Folder 15)
  - Poll books and election certificates (11th District), 1867. (Box 27, Folder 16)
  - Ballots, 1869. (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Poll lists (1st District), 1869. (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Poll lists (2nd District), 1869. (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Poll lists (3rd District), 1869. (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Poll lists (4th District), 1869. (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Poll lists (5th District), 1869. (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Poll lists (6th District), 1869. (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Poll lists (7th District), 1869. (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Poll lists (8th District), 1869. (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Poll lists (9th District), 1869. (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - Poll lists (10th District), 1869. (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - Poll lists (11th District), 1869. (Box 28, Folder 12)
- Powhatan County
  - Election certificates, 1867. (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Poll books (1st District), 1867. (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Poll books (2nd District), 1867. (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Poll books (3rd District), 1867. (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Poll books (4th District), 1867. (Box 29, Folder 5)
- Prince Edward County
  - Election certificates, 1867. (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Poll books (1st and 2nd Districts), 1867. (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Poll books (2nd and 3rd Districts), 1867. (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Poll books (5th District), 1867. (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Ballots, 1869. (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Poll lists (1st and 2nd Districts), 1869. (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - Poll lists (3rd and 4th Districts), 1869. (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - Poll lists (5th District), 1869. (Box 29, Folder 13)
- Prince George County
  - Election certificates, 1867. (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Poll books (All Districts), 1867. (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Ballots, 1869. (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Poll lists (1st and 2nd Districts), 1869. (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Poll lists (2nd and 3rd Districts), 1869. (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Poll lists (4th and 5th Districts), 1869. (Box 30, Folder 6)
- Prince William County
  - Poll books (All Districts), 1867. (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Ballots, 1869. (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Poll lists (1st and 2nd Districts), 1869. (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - Poll lists (3rd and 4th Districts), 1869. (Box 30, Folder 10)
- Princess Anne County
  - Election certificates, 1867. (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - Poll books (1st and 2nd Districts), 1867. (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - Poll books (3rd - 5th Districts), 1867. (Box 30, Folder 13)
  - Ballots, 1869. (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Poll lists (1st District), 1869. (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Poll lists (2nd District), 1869. (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Poll lists (3rd Districts), 1869. (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Poll lists (4th District), 1869. (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Poll lists (5th District), 1869. (Box 31, Folder 6)
- Pulaski County
  - Ballots, 1867. (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Election certificates, 1867. (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Poll books (All Districts), 1867. (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Ballots, 1869. (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Poll lists (1st District), 1869. (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - Poll lists (2nd District), 1869. (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - Poll lists (3rd District), 1869. (Box 31, Folder 13)
  - Poll lists (4th District), 1869. (Box 31, Folder 14)
- Rappahannock County
  - Ballots, 1867. (Box 31, Folder 15)
  - Election certificates, 1867. (Box 31, Folder 16)
  - Poll books (1st - 3rd Districts), 1867. (Box 31, Folder 17)
  - Poll books (4th and 5th Districts), 1867. (Box 31, Folder 18)
  - Ballots, 1869. (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Poll lists (1st District), 1869. (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Poll lists (2nd District), 1869. (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Poll lists (3rd District), 1869. (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Poll lists (4th District), 1869. (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Poll lists (5th District), 1869. (Box 32, Folder 6)
- Richmond County
  - Poll lists (1st - 4th Districts) [only records for this county], 1869. (Box 32, Folder 7)
- Roanoke County
  - Ballots, 1867. (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - Election certificates, 1867. (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - Poll books (1st and 2nd Districts), 1867. (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - Poll books (3rd and 4th Districts), 1867. (Box 32, Folder 11)
  - Ballots, 1869. (Box 32, Folder 12)
  - Poll lists (1st District), 1869. (Box 32, Folder 13)
  - Poll lists (2nd District), 1869. (Box 32, Folder 14)
  - Poll lists (3rd District), 1869. (Box 32, Folder 15)
  - Poll lists (4th District), 1869. (Box 32, Folder 16)
- Rockbridge County
  - Ballots, 1867. (Box 32, Folder 17)
  - Election certificates, 1867. (Box 32, Folder 18)
  - Poll books (1st and 2nd Districts), 1867. (Box 32, Folder 19)
  - Poll books (3rd and 4th Districts), 1867. (Box 32, Folder 20)
  - Poll books (5th - 7th Districts), 1867. (Box 32, Folder 21)
  - Ballots, 1869. (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Poll lists (1st District), 1869. (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Poll lists (2nd District), 1869. (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Poll lists (3rd District), 1869. (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - Poll lists (4th District), 1869. (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Poll lists (5th Distric), 1869. (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Poll lists (6th District), 1869. (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Poll lists (7th District), 1869. (Box 33, Folder 8)
- Rockingham County
  - Ballots, 1867. (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - Election certificates, 1867. (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - Poll books (1st District), 1867. (Box 33, Folder 11)
  - Poll books (2nd District), 1867. (Box 33, Folder 12)
  - Poll books (3rd District), 1867. (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Poll books (4th District), 1867. (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Poll books (5th District), 1867. (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Poll books (6th District), 1867. (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Poll books (7th District), 1867. (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - Poll books (8th District), 1867. (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Poll books (9th District), 1867. (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - Ballots, 1869. (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - Poll lists (1st District), 1869. (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - Poll lists (2nd District), 1869. (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - Poll lists (3rd District), 1869. (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Poll lists (4th District), 1869. (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Poll lists (5th District), 1869. (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Poll lists (6th District), 1869. (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Poll lists (7th District), 1869. (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - Poll lists (8th District), 1869. (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - Poll lists (9th District), 1869. (Box 35, Folder 5)
- Russell County
  - Ballots, 1867. (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - Election certificates, 1867. (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - Poll books (1st and 2nd Districts), 1867. (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - Poll books (3rd and 4th Districts), 1867. (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - Poll book (5th and 6th Districts), 1867. (Box 35, Folder 10)
  - Ballots, 1869. (Box 35, Folder 11)
  - Poll lists (1st District), 1869. (Box 35, Folder 12)
  - Poll lists (2nd District), 1869. (Box 35, Folder 13)
  - Poll lists (3rd District), 1869. (Box 35, Folder 14)
  - Poll lists (4th District), 1869. (Box 35, Folder 15)
  - Poll lists (5th District), 1869. (Box 35, Folder 16)
  - Poll lists (6th District), 1869. (Box 35, Folder 17)
- Scott County
  - Election certificates, 1867. (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - Poll books (1st and 2nd Districts), 1867. (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Poll books (3rd and 4th Districts), 1867. (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Poll books (5th and 6th Districts), 1867. (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Poll books (7th District), 1867. (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - Ballots, 1869. (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - Canvass return, 1869. (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - Poll lists (1st District), 1869. (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - Poll lists (2nd District), 1869. (Box 36, Folder 9)
  - Poll lists (3rd District), 1869. (Box 36, Folder 10)
  - Poll lists (4th District), 1869. (Box 36, Folder 11)
  - Poll lists (5th District), 1869. (Box 36, Folder 12)
  - Poll lists (6th District), 1869. (Box 36, Folder 13)
  - Poll lists (7th District), 1869. (Box 36, Folder 14)
- Shenandoah County
  - Ballots, 1867. (Box 36, Folder 15)
  - Election certificates, 1867. (Box 36, Folder 16)
  - Poll books (1st and 2nd Districts), 1867. (Box 36, Folder 17)
  - Poll books (3rd and 4th Districts), 1867. (Box 36, Folder 18)
  - Poll books (5th and 6th Districts), 1867. (Box 36, Folder 19)
  - Ballots, 1869. (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - Poll lists (1st District), 1869. (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - Poll lists (2nd District), 1869. (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - Poll lists (3rd District), 1869. (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - Poll lists (4th District), 1869. (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - Poll lists (5th District), 1869. (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - Poll lists (6th District), 1869. (Box 37, Folder 7)
- Southampton County
  - Ballots, 1867. (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - Election certificates, 1867. (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - Poll books (1st District), 1867. (Box 37, Folder 10)
  - Poll books (2nd District), 1867. (Box 37, Folder 11)
  - Poll books (3rd District), 1867. (Box 37, Folder 12)
  - Poll books (4th District), 1867. (Box 37, Folder 13)
  - Poll books (5th District), 1867. (Box 37, Folder 14)
  - Poll books (6th District), 1867. (Box 37, Folder 15)
  - Poll books (7th District), 1867. (Box 37, Folder 16)
  - Ballots, 1869. (Box 37, Folder 17)
  - Poll lists (1st District), 1869. (Box 37, Folder 18)
  - Poll lists (2nd District), 1869. (Box 37, Folder 19)
  - Poll lists (3rd District), 1869. (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - Poll lists (4th District), 1869. (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Poll lists (5th District), 1869. (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - Poll lists (6th and 7th Districts), 1869. (Box 38, Folder 4)
- Spotsylvania County
  - Correspondence, 1867. (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Election certificates, 1867. (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - Poll books (1st District), 1867. (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - Poll books (2nd District), 1867. (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - Poll books (3rd District), 1867. (Box 38, Folder 9)
  - Poll books (4th District), 1867. (Box 38, Folder 10)
  - Poll books (5th District), 1867. (Box 38, Folder 11)
  - Ballots, 1869. (Box 38, Folder 12)
  - Certificates of registration, 1869. (Box 38, Folder 13)
  - Poll lists (1st District), 1869. (Box 38, Folder 14)
  - Poll lists (2nd District), 1869. (Box 38, Folder 15)
  - Poll lists (3rd District), 1869. (Box 38, Folder 16)
  - Poll lists (4th District), 1869. (Box 38, Folder 17)
  - Poll lists (5th District), 1869. (Box 38, Folder 18)
- Stafford County
  - Election certificates, 1867. (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Poll books (1st and 2nd Districts), 1867. (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - ,Poll books (3rd and 4th Districts) 1867. (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Ballots, 1869. (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Poll lists (1st District), 1869. (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - Poll lists (2nd District), 1869. (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - Poll lists (3rd District), 1869. (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - Poll lists (4th District), 1869. (Box 39, Folder 8)
- Surry County
  - Election certificates, 1869. (Box 39, Folder 8a)
  - Poll books (All Districts), 1867. (Box 39, Folder 9)
  - Ballots, 1869. (Box 39, Folder 10)
  - Poll lists (1st District), 1869. (Box 39, Folder 11)
  - Poll lists (2nd District), 1869. (Box 39, Folder 12)
  - Poll lists (3rd and 4th Districts), 1869. (Box 39, Folder 13)
- Tazewell County
  - Election certificates, 1867. (Box 39, Folder 14)
  - Poll books (1st District), 1867. (Box 39, Folder 15)
  - Poll books (2nd District), 1867. (Box 39, Folder 16)
  - Poll books (3rd District), 1867. (Box 39, Folder 17)
  - Poll books (4th District), 1867. (Box 39, Folder 18)
  - Poll books (5th District), 1867. (Box 39, Folder 19)
  - Ballots, 1869. (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Poll lists (1st District), 1869. (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Poll lists (2nd District), 1869. (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - Poll lists (3rd District), 1869. (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - Poll lists (4th District), 1869. (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - Poll lists (5th District), 1869. (Box 40, Folder 6)
- Warren County
  - Ballots, 1867. (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - Ballots, 1869. (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - Poll lists (1st District), 1869. (Box 40, Folder 9)
  - Poll lists (2nd District), 1869. (Box 40, Folder 10)
  - Poll lists (3rd District), 1869. (Box 40, Folder 11)
  - Poll lists (4th District), 1869. (Box 40, Folder 12)
  - Poll lists (5th District), 1869. (Box 40, Folder 13)
- Warwick County
  - Election certificates, 1867. (Box 40, Folder 14)
  - Poll books (1st District), 1867. (Box 40, Folder 15)
  - Poll books (2nd District), 1867. (Box 40, Folder 16)
  - Poll books (3rd District), 1867. (Box 40, Folder 17)